aiawards.ie 2018-11-22

# Privacy Policy - AI Awards Ireland

By using the AI Awards website, you consent to the privacy policy and data practices described in this statement. 

By submitting an enquiry to us you are agreeing to the email marketing policy contained in the privacy policy. You may opt-out at any time by sending an email to [privacy@aiawards.ie](mailto:privacy@aiawards.ie)

Last update: 30th July 2018

Data Protection is a matter of Trust and Respect. We respect you and that includes your data and we put the utmost value in your Trust. Protecting your Data and respecting your privacy is at the core of every decision we make.

The AI Awards use a SSL certificate issued by Blacknight and request to all applicants not to submit confidential information as part of the application process. All data will be stored on Google via a Google Form. Once the competition has been finished the data will be deleted. 

## General Statement 

The body responsible for the collection of your data is AI Awards Limited by guarantee (“AI Awards”, “we”, “our” or “us”) a company registered in Ireland under company number 626063 trading as AI Awards Limited by Guarantee from a trading address at 23 Fitzwilliam Street Upper, Dublin 2.

If you have any questions regarding this policy or if you wish to exercise any of your rights concerning your data you can contact us by email [privacy@aiawards.ie](mailto:privacy@aiawards.ie). 

This statement relates to our privacy and cookie practices in connection with our website [www.aiawards.ie](https://www.aiawards.ie/). We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. Any external links to other websites are clearly identifiable as such. We ask that you read this privacy and cookie policy (‘Policy’) carefully as it contains important information about how we use cookies and will use your personal data.

### Personal Data

When you visit and/or register on The Site, we may collect and process information about you. This information will include information you may be asked to provide about yourself by filling in forms on the Site or by corresponding with us. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, personal description. (‘Personal Information’).

Like most websites, we automatically gather statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregate basis of all visitors to the Site. The information obtained in this way is purely statistical and only used in aggregate form. It cannot be used to identify you (‘Non-personal Information’).

To collect and process the information we need to process your entry in the competition, we use Google – read [Google’s privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). They have committed to be GDPR compliant and use the highest level of security available to protect data.

Applications are made to the AI Awards and processed through the website. The applications are hosted on a google form.  The Google Form can be accessed by volunteers of the AI Awards. The people this relates to is Mark Kelly and Liam McNamara. 

The judging panel will be able to access the application’s information to their respective categories that they are judging via the Google form for a period of 72 hours for judging purposes only. Please check the website for list of judges. Once the initial judging process has been completed the link to the Google form will no longer be accessible.

If you or your Company has been successful to the second part of the process – the presentation stage – you will bring additional information with you to present on your application. This information will not be stored and the applicant will be in charge of the presentation of this data. The data will not be transferred to another country and is not backed up anywhere other than the Google Form.

### Use of your Information

If you submit information to this Site and you choose to receive further information from us, we may use the information you provide us with for the following purposes:

  * To provide you with the information about AI Awards tickets, upcoming Meetups, podcasts and newsletters that you request from us
  * To contact you to tell you about important updates, changes or developments to the Site or our services, or to obtain your views on our services;
  * To monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us to develop the design and layout of the Site;
  * To  employ other companies and individuals, such as the AI Awards judges, to perform functions on our behalf such as analysing data, providing marketing assistance and designing and operating the Site. Such companies and individuals only have access to your personal information for the purpose of strictly carrying out this work. These companies will not use your data for any other purpose. AI Awards uses one data processor which is Google to store the data. Google is the only one for the web site traffic. 
  * To analyse information provided by the Site users to help us administer, support, and improve our business through Google Analytics.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. . You can Opt-out of these emails at any time by using the unsubscribe button at the bottom of any of our e-mails to you. 

### Disclosure of Personal Data 

Any information that you share with us will be stored and managed by us with the greatest care. We never share (rent, sell, or exchange) Personal Data with Third Parties for the purposes of allowing them to market products and services to you notwithstanding the provisions stipulated in this document. However, we do engage the services of third party service providers, which act as Data Processors, to assist us with our marketing activities.

We may need to disclose personal information if required by subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes, or law enforcement agencies or other third party agencies, companies and organisations in connection with any legal investigation to help prevent unlawful activity, to protect our property, safety, or to establish or exercise our legal rights, and those of our visitors, clients, or others (including for the purposes of fraud protection) or to such entities in order to comply with any legal obligations. 

We may provide links from time to time on the Site to other websites which are not within our control. Once you have left the AI Awards Site, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small file sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer‘s hard drive to identify you as the user of the Site. Many internet sites use cookies. By using this Site and agreeing to this Privacy Statement and Cookies Policy, you consent to the AI Awards use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Statement and Cookies Policy.

The site uses cookies to keep track of your access to [aiawards.ie](https://aiawards.ie/). We may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your Browsing interests. Your consent to the use of cookies will be obtained by you positively indicating your acceptance of our Terms of Use, this Privacy and Cookies Policy when you register with the AI Awards and/or by your browser settings and/ or by you ticking the relevant box confirming that you understand. 

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of this Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit this Site. Cookies make your experience easier by saving your preferences.

For more information generally on cookies, including how to disable them, please refer to [aboutcookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/). You will also find details on how to delete cookies from your computer.

### Cookies List

### Changes to Policy 

We reserve the right to change or amend this Policy from time to time. We encourage you to check this Policy occasionally to ensure you are aware of the most recent version that will apply each time you access this website. We will inform you by email of any changes to the data policy. 

The Effective Date of this Privacy Statement and Cookies Policy shall be displayed at the start of this document and from that date shall take the place of any previously published Privacy Statement and Cookies Policy.

### Limitation of Liability

Under no circumstances, including but not limited to negligence, shall we be liable for any special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, the website and the materials in it. Without detracting the aforementioned, in no event shall our total liability exceed the amount paid by you, if any, for accessing the site.

### Governing Law & Jurisdiction  

This Policy and all issues regarding our website are governed by the laws of Ireland and are subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Ireland.

### Definitions & References

Some definition and Reference to help you navigate this policy.  
Personal Data: means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person; (as per European regulation (EU) 2016/679 – GDPR).

Non Personal Data: means any information that is not related to an identified or identifiable natural person. In other words, any information that is not Personal Data, this is often referred to “Anonymized Data”.

Data Processors: means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the AI Awards (ie: controller); (as per European regulation (EU) 2016/679 – GDPR).

Marketing Sources: a set of information we collected in Cookies related to your interaction with our Marketing campaigns.

### Confidential Data

Take note that when submitting project information, please do not share confidential information or data.

It is important to note that no one should submit any information or data that is in any way critical or that represents anything that cannot be shared to a group of judges and advisors. In relation to IP, it is up to the applicant to protect the Intellectual Property. Please do not share IP. The AI Awards states clearly that applicants should not share any confidential information via the application form. 

Applicants can submit data and charts but only for a specific project and never including any sensitive or critical data. The data will be stored in the cloud and once the competition is closed the data will be deleted. The data is never shared beyond Google and with our Model Contract Clause with Google, they will delete the data from their service. There are no other clouds used other than Google.

Do not submit any data or information that relates to a person or group of persons and/or any information that can be used to identify a person and/or group of persons.

AI Awards will do our best to protect your personal data and projects submitted to the website. However, unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. 

AI Awards cannot be held responsible for the security and integrity of your personal devices and connection to the internet. Taking this into consideration we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the site; any transmission is at your own risk. For this reason, AI Awards does not take any responsibility for information that has been submitted.

 **If you have any further queries, please contact[liam@aiawards.ie](mailto:liam@aiawards.ie) before you make any applications.**

AI Awards uses cookies to improve your browsing experience. By continuing to use the site, you agree to the use of cookies. To find out how to manage and disable cookies please read our -[Privacy Policy](https://aiawards.ie/privacy-policy/). Accept
